{
    "0": {
        "answer": "72/77", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "67/77", 
            "1": "74/77", 
            "2": "73/77", 
            "3": "72/77"
        }, 
        "question": "29/77 + 43/77", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "1": {
        "answer": "71/73", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "67/73", 
            "1": "75/73", 
            "2": "71/73", 
            "3": "71/73"
        }, 
        "question": "57/73 + 14/73", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "2": {
        "answer": "81/54", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "84/54", 
            "1": "86/54", 
            "2": "82/54", 
            "3": "81/54"
        }, 
        "question": "42/54 + 39/54", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "3": {
        "answer": "134/84", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "137/84", 
            "1": "136/84", 
            "2": "137/84", 
            "3": "134/84"
        }, 
        "question": "82/84 + 52/84", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "4": {
        "answer": "100/63", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "105/63", 
            "1": "104/63", 
            "2": "103/63", 
            "3": "100/63"
        }, 
        "question": "51/63 + 49/63", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "5": {
        "answer": "81/67", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "81/67", 
            "1": "79/67", 
            "2": "77/67", 
            "3": "81/67"
        }, 
        "question": "25/67 + 56/67", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "6": {
        "answer": "76/71", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "76/71", 
            "1": "77/71", 
            "2": "78/71", 
            "3": "76/71"
        }, 
        "question": "22/71 + 54/71", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "7": {
        "answer": "45/63", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "45/63", 
            "1": "47/63", 
            "2": "50/63", 
            "3": "45/63"
        }, 
        "question": "35/63 + 10/63", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "8": {
        "answer": "97/69", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "100/69", 
            "1": "92/69", 
            "2": "102/69", 
            "3": "97/69"
        }, 
        "question": "55/69 + 42/69", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "9": {
        "answer": "72/66", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "69/66", 
            "1": "67/66", 
            "2": "74/66", 
            "3": "72/66"
        }, 
        "question": "36/66 + 36/66", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "10": {
        "answer": "70/70", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "73/70", 
            "1": "71/70", 
            "2": "72/70", 
            "3": "70/70"
        }, 
        "question": "19/70 + 51/70", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "11": {
        "answer": "72/99", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "76/99", 
            "1": "73/99", 
            "2": "70/99", 
            "3": "72/99"
        }, 
        "question": "34/99 + 38/99", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "12": {
        "answer": "152/85", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "156/85", 
            "1": "151/85", 
            "2": "156/85", 
            "3": "152/85"
        }, 
        "question": "72/85 + 80/85", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "13": {
        "answer": "45/58", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "49/58", 
            "1": "49/58", 
            "2": "49/58", 
            "3": "45/58"
        }, 
        "question": "6/58 + 39/58", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "14": {
        "answer": "65/99", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "62/99", 
            "1": "65/99", 
            "2": "70/99", 
            "3": "65/99"
        }, 
        "question": "20/99 + 45/99", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "15": {
        "answer": "13/64", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "12/64", 
            "1": "14/64", 
            "2": "16/64", 
            "3": "13/64"
        }, 
        "question": "3/64 + 10/64", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "16": {
        "answer": "30/63", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "35/63", 
            "1": "26/63", 
            "2": "33/63", 
            "3": "30/63"
        }, 
        "question": "15/63 + 15/63", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "17": {
        "answer": "101/89", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "99/89", 
            "1": "102/89", 
            "2": "98/89", 
            "3": "101/89"
        }, 
        "question": "53/89 + 48/89", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "18": {
        "answer": "70/94", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "70/94", 
            "1": "74/94", 
            "2": "72/94", 
            "3": "70/94"
        }, 
        "question": "66/94 + 4/94", 
        "result": false
    }, 
    "19": {
        "answer": "51/61", 
        "answerSelected": "", 
        "options": {
            "0": "49/61", 
            "1": "49/61", 
            "2": "51/61", 
            "3": "51/61"
        }, 
        "question": "37/61 + 14/61", 
        "result": false
    }
}
